{"uuid": "5ddef6a7-812c-4d7f-a9f2-4075d033857b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "COC(=O)c1ccc(Cl)nn1", "smiles_random": "O(C)C(=O)c1ccc(Cl)nn1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO(C)C(=O)c1ccc(Cl)nn1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "COC(=O)c1ccc(Cl)nn1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "1003ae77-3566-4a82-8d05-0c06e7db579f", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1ccc2ccc(Cl)nc2n1", "smiles_random": "c1cc(nc2c1ccc(C)n2)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1cc(nc2c1ccc(C)n2)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1ccc2ccc(Cl)nc2n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "4122842f-3d6a-4215-b006-ca0a0ef52618", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "OC1CCCC1n1cccn1", "smiles_random": "c1ccn(n1)C1C(CCC1)O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1ccn(n1)C1C(CCC1)O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "OC1CCCC1n1cccn1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "60f87653-5dbe-49de-85ae-1581c1fe8cb6", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=C(NCc1cccnc1)C1CC=CC1", "smiles_random": "C1(CC=CC1)C(=O)NCc1cnccc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1(CC=CC1)C(=O)NCc1cnccc1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=C(NCc1cccnc1)C1CC=CC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "e448967d-6222-4ff6-83fa-ff2ac235fd3d", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(C=Cc1ccc(Cl)cc1)=NO", "smiles_random": "c1(C=CC(C)=NO)ccc(Cl)cc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(C=CC(C)=NO)ccc(Cl)cc1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(C=Cc1ccc(Cl)cc1)=NO", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "6e29f172-142c-4dce-a415-d945dd3a38f2", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(=O)C(C)CC(C)(O)c1ccccc1", "smiles_random": "c1c(cccc1)C(C)(CC(C)C(C)=O)O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(cccc1)C(C)(CC(C)C(C)=O)O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(=O)C(C)CC(C)(O)c1ccccc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "f99e001b-03ed-4bd7-9216-3c121117548a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1ccc(CCNC(C)c2ccncc2)cc1", "smiles_random": "c1(C(C)NCCc2ccc(C)cc2)ccncc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(C(C)NCCc2ccc(C)cc2)ccncc1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1ccc(CCNC(C)c2ccncc2)cc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "186cecd8-d6d7-4f61-84c0-272020a6171f", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1ccnc2c1nc(N)n2C1CCCOC1", "smiles_random": "c1cc(c2nc(n(C3COCCC3)c2n1)N)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1cc(c2nc(n(C3COCCC3)c2n1)N)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1ccnc2c1nc(N)n2C1CCCOC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "2c2e31ae-7eae-4601-94d9-49838e19bede", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(C)CC(NC(=O)C1CC1)c1cccs1", "smiles_random": "c1cc(sc1)C(NC(C1CC1)=O)CC(C)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1cc(sc1)C(NC(C1CC1)=O)CC(C)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(C)CC(NC(=O)C1CC1)c1cccs1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "a82ac021-f3b5-4eda-8bfa-ae530a970a73", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCSCCC(=O)N1CCC(O)(C(F)(F)F)CC1", "smiles_random": "C1(C(F)(F)F)(CCN(CC1)C(CCSCC)=O)O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1(C(F)(F)F)(CCN(CC1)C(CCSCC)=O)O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCSCCC(=O)N1CCC(O)(C(F)(F)F)CC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "b37771c3-ec1e-478c-8147-4aa7e377ddff", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "COC1CCCC(OC(=O)c2cccc3cc[nH]c23)C1", "smiles_random": "O(C(=O)c1c2c(cc[nH]2)ccc1)C1CCCC(OC)C1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO(C(=O)c1c2c(cc[nH]2)ccc1)C1CCCC(OC)C1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "COC1CCCC(OC(=O)c2cccc3cc[nH]c23)C1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "df46b97c-d4b5-410e-9f74-2091e23dd9be", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1cc(Cl)ncc1NC(=O)N1CCC(C)C(O)C1", "smiles_random": "Cc1cc(Cl)ncc1NC(N1CC(O)C(C)CC1)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCc1cc(Cl)ncc1NC(N1CC(O)C(C)CC1)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1cc(Cl)ncc1NC(=O)N1CCC(C)C(O)C1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "cb5309c4-eb70-4cf3-b311-e2017463d0b9", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC1CN(C(=O)c2cc3ccccc3c(Cl)n2)C(C)(C)CO1", "smiles_random": "C1(OCC(N(C(=O)c2nc(Cl)c3ccccc3c2)C1)(C)C)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1(OCC(N(C(=O)c2nc(Cl)c3ccccc3c2)C1)(C)C)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC1CN(C(=O)c2cc3ccccc3c(Cl)n2)C(C)(C)CO1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "b402a812-905b-4aba-86d8-961486ae099d", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCN(Cc1cccc(C)c1)C(=O)NCC#Cc1ccccc1", "smiles_random": "C(c1cc(C)ccc1)N(C(=O)NCC#Cc1ccccc1)CC"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(c1cc(C)ccc1)N(C(=O)NCC#Cc1ccccc1)CC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCN(Cc1cccc(C)c1)C(=O)NCC#Cc1ccccc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "65bfb215-61b6-4470-9a98-545e84d649b3", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCOC(=O)NN=C1C(=O)Nc2ccc(Br)cc21", "smiles_random": "C(=O)(OCC)NN=C1C(Nc2ccc(Br)cc12)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(=O)(OCC)NN=C1C(Nc2ccc(Br)cc12)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCOC(=O)NN=C1C(=O)Nc2ccc(Br)cc21", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "a74d4ed1-b380-4017-b912-a24ee8591f83", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=C(Cc1ccc(Cl)cc1)NC1C(c2ccccc2)CC(O)C1O", "smiles_random": "C(C(NC1C(c2ccccc2)CC(C1O)O)=O)c1ccc(cc1)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(C(NC1C(c2ccccc2)CC(C1O)O)=O)c1ccc(cc1)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=C(Cc1ccc(Cl)cc1)NC1C(c2ccccc2)CC(O)C1O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "46848258-4abd-4cbf-975f-30f6685a473c", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(CNC(=O)C1(C)CC1(Cl)Cl)c1nc(-c2ccccc2)no1", "smiles_random": "c1(ccccc1)-c1noc(n1)C(C)CNC(C1(C)CC1(Cl)Cl)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(ccccc1)-c1noc(n1)C(C)CNC(C1(C)CC1(Cl)Cl)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(CNC(=O)C1(C)CC1(Cl)Cl)c1nc(-c2ccccc2)no1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "b962a6f1-0842-4492-8cb9-76340616d943", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCC(=O)NCCOc1ccc2nnc(-c3ccccc3)n2n1", "smiles_random": "O(c1ccc2n(n1)c(-c1ccccc1)nn2)CCNC(CCC)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO(c1ccc2n(n1)c(-c1ccccc1)nn2)CCNC(CCC)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCC(=O)NCCOc1ccc2nnc(-c3ccccc3)n2n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "5364e11e-13a6-4dda-855c-ae93575f4da7", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCc1ccc(-c2nc(C)c(C(=O)Nc3ccc(NC(C)=O)cc3)s2)cc1", "smiles_random": "C(C)(Nc1ccc(NC(c2c(C)nc(s2)-c2ccc(cc2)CC)=O)cc1)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(C)(Nc1ccc(NC(c2c(C)nc(s2)-c2ccc(cc2)CC)=O)cc1)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCc1ccc(-c2nc(C)c(C(=O)Nc3ccc(NC(C)=O)cc3)s2)cc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "438e0a68-963f-42af-a52b-28c9cf5b86a7", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "COc1ccc(C(=O)N2N=C(c3ccc(OC)cc3)CC2(O)C(F)(F)F)cc1", "smiles_random": "N1(C(=O)c2ccc(OC)cc2)C(O)(C(F)(F)F)CC(c2ccc(cc2)OC)=N1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nN1(C(=O)c2ccc(OC)cc2)C(O)(C(F)(F)F)CC(c2ccc(cc2)OC)=N1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "COc1ccc(C(=O)N2N=C(c3ccc(OC)cc3)CC2(O)C(F)(F)F)cc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "e7857db2-c27a-426d-86ce-a70bc7551751", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1cccc2nc(C(=O)OC(C)C(=O)NC3CCOc4ccccc43)cn12", "smiles_random": "O=C(NC1c2c(OCC1)cccc2)C(C)OC(=O)c1nc2n(c1)c(C)ccc2"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO=C(NC1c2c(OCC1)cccc2)C(C)OC(=O)c1nc2n(c1)c(C)ccc2\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1cccc2nc(C(=O)OC(C)C(=O)NC3CCOc4ccccc43)cn12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "fbcfd1af-1261-4642-afb1-6e4a775d7f64", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=C(CN1CCCN(Cc2ccccc2Cl)S1(=O)=O)N1CCCCCC1", "smiles_random": "C1CCCN(CC1)C(CN1CCCN(S1(=O)=O)Cc1ccccc1Cl)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1CCCN(CC1)C(CN1CCCN(S1(=O)=O)Cc1ccccc1Cl)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=C(CN1CCCN(Cc2ccccc2Cl)S1(=O)=O)N1CCCCCC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "5b9f7feb-d526-4bfe-902b-24cc55d5f1b5", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(NC(=O)C1CCN(C(=O)N2CCOc3ccc(Cl)cc32)CC1)c1ccccc1", "smiles_random": "C1(CCN(CC1)C(N1CCOc2ccc(cc21)Cl)=O)C(=O)NC(c1ccccc1)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1(CCN(CC1)C(N1CCOc2ccc(cc21)Cl)=O)C(=O)NC(c1ccccc1)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(NC(=O)C1CCN(C(=O)N2CCOc3ccc(Cl)cc32)CC1)c1ccccc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "df10f59c-eefe-43ae-8a9c-a15c01a922c6", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cn1c(SCc2nc3ccccc3c(=O)n2Cc2ccco2)nc2ccccc21", "smiles_random": "c1ccc(o1)Cn1c(c2c(nc1CSc1nc3ccccc3n1C)cccc2)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1ccc(o1)Cn1c(c2c(nc1CSc1nc3ccccc3n1C)cccc2)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cn1c(SCc2nc3ccccc3c(=O)n2Cc2ccco2)nc2ccccc21", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "46cf1478-6261-45fb-921f-2662cb6fd567", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "C=CCn1c(=NC(=O)c2ccc3ncsc3c2)sc2cc(S(N)(=O)=O)ccc21", "smiles_random": "c12c(ccc(S(=O)(N)=O)c2)n(c(s1)=NC(c1ccc2ncsc2c1)=O)CC=C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc12c(ccc(S(=O)(N)=O)c2)n(c(s1)=NC(c1ccc2ncsc2c1)=O)CC=C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "C=CCn1c(=NC(=O)c2ccc3ncsc3c2)sc2cc(S(N)(=O)=O)ccc21", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "002b6da1-b4e0-4f3b-b556-9dba5c2abf59", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=C(c1ccccc1Cl)N1CCN(S(=O)(=O)c2ccc(Br)s2)CC1", "smiles_random": "c1cc(Cl)c(cc1)C(=O)N1CCN(S(=O)(=O)c2ccc(Br)s2)CC1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1cc(Cl)c(cc1)C(=O)N1CCN(S(=O)(=O)c2ccc(Br)s2)CC1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=C(c1ccccc1Cl)N1CCN(S(=O)(=O)c2ccc(Br)s2)CC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "017028c8-fe08-4cec-9c70-a91b7d944282", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=C(CCc1cccc(Cl)c1Cl)Nc1cc(N2CCCS2(=O)=O)ccc1Cl", "smiles_random": "C(c1c(Cl)c(ccc1)Cl)CC(=O)Nc1c(ccc(c1)N1CCCS1(=O)=O)Cl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(c1c(Cl)c(ccc1)Cl)CC(=O)Nc1c(ccc(c1)N1CCCS1(=O)=O)Cl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=C(CCc1cccc(Cl)c1Cl)Nc1cc(N2CCCS2(=O)=O)ccc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "fade95d4-dc49-48a2-9a09-9c1c5ff6a206", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=C(c1sc2cc(Cl)ccc2c1Cl)N(Cc1ccc(F)cc1)C1CCS(=O)(=O)C1", "smiles_random": "C1(CCS(C1)(=O)=O)N(C(c1c(c2c(s1)cc(Cl)cc2)Cl)=O)Cc1ccc(cc1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1(CCS(C1)(=O)=O)N(C(c1c(c2c(s1)cc(Cl)cc2)Cl)=O)Cc1ccc(cc1)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=C(c1sc2cc(Cl)ccc2c1Cl)N(Cc1ccc(F)cc1)C1CCS(=O)(=O)C1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "c0d1797f-ebf9-488e-a90a-bd60ab428dbe", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCOC(=O)c1nn(-c2ccccc2)c(=O)cc1NC(=O)c1ccc(I)cc1", "smiles_random": "N(c1c(C(OCC)=O)nn(-c2ccccc2)c(c1)=O)C(c1ccc(cc1)I)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nN(c1c(C(OCC)=O)nn(-c2ccccc2)c(c1)=O)C(c1ccc(cc1)I)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCOC(=O)c1nn(-c2ccccc2)c(=O)cc1NC(=O)c1ccc(I)cc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "cfbdc8d4-ea6e-4f55-ac7a-50f66ebda333", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCOC(=O)N1CCc2nc(NC(=O)C3CCCN3S(=O)(=O)c3cccs3)sc2C1", "smiles_random": "c12CN(CCc1nc(s2)NC(C1N(S(c2sccc2)(=O)=O)CCC1)=O)C(=O)OCC"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc12CN(CCc1nc(s2)NC(C1N(S(c2sccc2)(=O)=O)CCC1)=O)C(=O)OCC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCOC(=O)N1CCc2nc(NC(=O)C3CCCN3S(=O)(=O)c3cccs3)sc2C1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "7ed245b4-6907-4762-b749-ebfee8df946f", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=Cc1cc(C(=O)CCl)c[nH]1", "smiles_random": "C(c1c[nH]c(C=O)c1)(=O)CCl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(c1c[nH]c(C=O)c1)(=O)CCl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=Cc1cc(C(=O)CCl)c[nH]1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "13f40574-41ab-4bd9-bf99-2651632e4bee", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(NC(=O)C1CCCO1)C1CC1", "smiles_random": "C1COC(C(=O)NC(C2CC2)C)C1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1COC(C(=O)NC(C2CC2)C)C1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(NC(=O)C1CCCO1)C1CC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "c32f4aba-bebf-451f-8050-f99746d7ab07", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "COC(=O)c1ccc(F)c(F)c1", "smiles_random": "C(c1cc(F)c(cc1)F)(=O)OC"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(c1cc(F)c(cc1)F)(=O)OC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "COC(=O)c1ccc(F)c(F)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "b3c69a19-dd74-4279-aeae-3b18d487e7e5", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCNC1(C#N)CCC(C)CC1", "smiles_random": "N#CC1(NCC)CCC(C)CC1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nN#CC1(NCC)CCC(C)CC1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCNC1(C#N)CCC(C)CC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "7b220292-9ecf-4dd0-a3b8-066cbae0e021", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCC(=O)c1ccc(F)c(F)c1", "smiles_random": "c1(F)c(cc(C(CC)=O)cc1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(F)c(cc(C(CC)=O)cc1)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCC(=O)c1ccc(F)c(F)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "e05642d2-27c3-4017-b810-5db005036191", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Nc1ncc(F)cc1C#CCO", "smiles_random": "c1c(c(N)ncc1F)C#CCO"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(c(N)ncc1F)C#CCO\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Nc1ncc(F)cc1C#CCO", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "da3ba5b2-b07e-4356-904a-005b9c35afe8", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Nc1cncnc1NCC1CCC1", "smiles_random": "n1cnc(c(N)c1)NCC1CCC1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1cnc(c(N)c1)NCC1CCC1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Nc1cncnc1NCC1CCC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "6629d0de-fcf8-4a49-b735-5bc7912a9be1", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCC(C)CC(C)N1CC(=O)NC1=O", "smiles_random": "C(CC(CC)C)(N1CC(=O)NC1=O)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(CC(CC)C)(N1CC(=O)NC1=O)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCC(C)CC(C)N1CC(=O)NC1=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "b801d50f-7c5e-46b9-8b68-a7c8844936b7", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "N#Cc1cccc(-c2ccc(N)cn2)n1", "smiles_random": "c1(-c2ncc(cc2)N)cccc(n1)C#N"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(-c2ncc(cc2)N)cccc(n1)C#N\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "N#Cc1cccc(-c2ccc(N)cn2)n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "a52ebd57-4a9e-4789-9f7a-449370d82c50", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "ClCC1CCCOC1c1cccnc1", "smiles_random": "O1C(c2cccnc2)C(CCC1)CCl"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO1C(c2cccnc2)C(CCC1)CCl\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "ClCC1CCCOC1c1cccnc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "35519b74-9db7-4aa2-9bb6-4fa47bb1da6e", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCOCCC(=O)Nc1[nH]ncc1N", "smiles_random": "O(CCC(=O)Nc1c(N)cn[nH]1)CCC"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO(CCC(=O)Nc1c(N)cn[nH]1)CCC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCOCCC(=O)Nc1[nH]ncc1N", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "eec9a9b1-8f90-4eaf-b8c3-668e1c6ea0bd", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC1(C)C(=O)NCCN1Cc1cc[nH]c1", "smiles_random": "c1cc(c[nH]1)CN1C(C)(C)C(=O)NCC1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1cc(c[nH]1)CN1C(C)(C)C(=O)NCC1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC1(C)C(=O)NCCN1Cc1cc[nH]c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "eece74f4-09c1-41ed-a59b-2722f801e4ed", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCCOCc1cnc(NN)s1", "smiles_random": "CCCCOCc1sc(NN)nc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCCCCOCc1sc(NN)nc1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCCOCc1cnc(NN)s1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "62814d1d-7194-4ca6-9cb2-aa098d7fa6e2", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=C1Cc2cc(C(F)(F)F)ccc2N1", "smiles_random": "C1c2c(ccc(c2)C(F)(F)F)NC1=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1c2c(ccc(c2)C(F)(F)F)NC1=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=C1Cc2cc(C(F)(F)F)ccc2N1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "de4f7020-122a-460b-a14f-7be64c860659", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC1CCCC(N2CCOC(C(N)=NO)C2)C1", "smiles_random": "C(C1CN(CCO1)C1CCCC(C1)C)(N)=NO"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(C1CN(CCO1)C1CCCC(C1)C)(N)=NO\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC1CCCC(N2CCOC(C(N)=NO)C2)C1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "2381e797-7bb7-4b40-b9d6-ac40deda739a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(C)C(NCc1ncnn1C)c1cccnc1", "smiles_random": "c1(CNC(c2cccnc2)C(C)C)n(ncn1)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(CNC(c2cccnc2)C(C)C)n(ncn1)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(C)C(NCc1ncnn1C)c1cccnc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "29f449c1-4da5-4a34-b885-78c3583636e3", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "COCCCNC(=O)c1cccc2cccnc12", "smiles_random": "c1ccc(C(=O)NCCCOC)c2c1cccn2"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1ccc(C(=O)NCCCOC)c2c1cccn2\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "COCCCNC(=O)c1cccc2cccnc12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "77185b6d-f93c-45f2-a1a5-258f8d1fbd7f", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CN1C(=O)NCC1c1ccc(C(C)(C)C)cc1", "smiles_random": "C1C(N(C(=O)N1)C)c1ccc(cc1)C(C)(C)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1C(N(C(=O)N1)C)c1ccc(cc1)C(C)(C)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CN1C(=O)NCC1c1ccc(C(C)(C)C)cc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "e070eac6-ba0f-4bba-b443-6f23252dfeeb", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(Cl)C(=O)N(C)C1(C#N)CCCCC1", "smiles_random": "C1CCCC(C1)(C#N)N(C(C(Cl)C)=O)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1CCCC(C1)(C#N)N(C(C(Cl)C)=O)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(Cl)C(=O)N(C)C1(C#N)CCCCC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "76240f34-c100-4eec-ba5d-d21f7ca05f5e", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1ccccc1C(=O)NCc1cccc(C#N)c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(CNC(=O)c2ccccc2C)cc(C#N)cc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(CNC(=O)c2ccccc2C)cc(C#N)cc1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1ccccc1C(=O)NCc1cccc(C#N)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "a5f4116b-6007-433d-8aae-9f6810f349ef", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCC(C#N)C1(O)CCCC(C(F)(F)F)C1", "smiles_random": "FC(F)(C1CCCC(C1)(O)C(CC)C#N)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nFC(F)(C1CCCC(C1)(O)C(CC)C#N)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCC(C#N)C1(O)CCCC(C(F)(F)F)C1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "a1b7aeeb-346c-4a2b-a1f4-afca6ae0b2b2", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "N#CC1(C(O)c2ccccc2Cl)CCc2ccccc21", "smiles_random": "c12ccccc1CCC2(C(c1ccccc1Cl)O)C#N"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc12ccccc1CCC2(C(c1ccccc1Cl)O)C#N\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "N#CC1(C(O)c2ccccc2Cl)CCc2ccccc21", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "280c4f1a-4a89-48a0-8856-bd738913b19a", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Clc1nccc(N2CCC(N3CCOCC3)C2)n1", "smiles_random": "n1c(ccnc1Cl)N1CC(CC1)N1CCOCC1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1c(ccnc1Cl)N1CC(CC1)N1CCOCC1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Clc1nccc(N2CCC(N3CCOCC3)C2)n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "be6cd801-3728-48a0-888d-b8dead21f72c", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Oc1ccc(-c2nc3ccccc3s2)cc1Cl", "smiles_random": "s1c2c(cccc2)nc1-c1ccc(O)c(Cl)c1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\ns1c2c(cccc2)nc1-c1ccc(O)c(Cl)c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Oc1ccc(-c2nc3ccccc3s2)cc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "aa21dce7-abc0-47e5-ad16-b3322e28676d", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1cccc(SC(C(N)=O)c2ccccc2)c1", "smiles_random": "c1cc(C)cc(SC(c2ccccc2)C(N)=O)c1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1cc(C)cc(SC(c2ccccc2)C(N)=O)c1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1cccc(SC(C(N)=O)c2ccccc2)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "32e9dceb-f985-4349-ac0b-8ce2e88f152b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=C(COc1ccccc1)Nc1ccc2ccccc2c1", "smiles_random": "c1c2ccc(NC(COc3ccccc3)=O)cc2ccc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c2ccc(NC(COc3ccccc3)=O)cc2ccc1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=C(COc1ccccc1)Nc1ccc2ccccc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "f62fe64a-b35d-43df-b925-c3a40a6893ab", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(CS(C)(=O)=O)N(C)C(=O)c1cccc(Cl)c1", "smiles_random": "O=S(=O)(C)CC(N(C(c1cc(Cl)ccc1)=O)C)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO=S(=O)(C)CC(N(C(c1cc(Cl)ccc1)=O)C)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(CS(C)(=O)=O)N(C)C(=O)c1cccc(Cl)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "a6f4882b-a8a9-46ef-b31a-074fcb5e7700", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1ccn(CC(=O)NC(C)c2nc3ccccc3o2)n1", "smiles_random": "n1c2c(cccc2)oc1C(C)NC(Cn1ccc(n1)C)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1c2c(cccc2)oc1C(C)NC(Cn1ccc(n1)C)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1ccn(CC(=O)NC(C)c2nc3ccccc3o2)n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "2fc00bb0-2a42-4a30-8c17-80403fe88c4f", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCNC(=O)Nc1ccc(C(=O)N2CCC(C)CC2)cc1", "smiles_random": "c1c(NC(=O)NCCC)ccc(c1)C(N1CCC(C)CC1)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(NC(=O)NCCC)ccc(c1)C(N1CCC(C)CC1)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCNC(=O)Nc1ccc(C(=O)N2CCC(C)CC2)cc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "0684fd1c-cf6b-4c9a-a510-ccf7d205c516", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC1(CNC(=O)C2=Cc3cc(F)ccc3OC2)CCCS1", "smiles_random": "C1(C(=O)NCC2(C)SCCC2)COc2c(cc(F)cc2)C=1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1(C(=O)NCC2(C)SCCC2)COc2c(cc(F)cc2)C=1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC1(CNC(=O)C2=Cc3cc(F)ccc3OC2)CCCS1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "f9b63099-dd35-4989-b450-0d52a782e7eb", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "COc1ccc(S(=O)(=O)NC2CCCCCCC2)cc1", "smiles_random": "c1c(ccc(c1)S(=O)(=O)NC1CCCCCCC1)OC"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(ccc(c1)S(=O)(=O)NC1CCCCCCC1)OC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "COc1ccc(S(=O)(=O)NC2CCCCCCC2)cc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "667a606c-fd19-4670-8d4a-ef325cb6ec0b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1cc(NC(=O)C2COc3ccccc3O2)c2ncccc2c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(C)cc(c2ncccc12)NC(=O)C1COc2ccccc2O1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(C)cc(c2ncccc12)NC(=O)C1COc2ccccc2O1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1cc(NC(=O)C2COc3ccccc3O2)c2ncccc2c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "e2b7642d-5081-4058-b25f-e68b00c79219", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(Cc1ccccc1)C(=O)NCc1cn(-c2ccccc2)nn1", "smiles_random": "c1cc(CC(C)C(=O)NCc2cn(-c3ccccc3)nn2)ccc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1cc(CC(C)C(=O)NCc2cn(-c3ccccc3)nn2)ccc1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(Cc1ccccc1)C(=O)NCc1cn(-c2ccccc2)nn1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "f089d4f7-15e1-48b0-a82c-af46fa41cc7d", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=C(NC1CCSc2ccc(F)cc21)C(O)c1ccccc1", "smiles_random": "c1cccc(c1)C(C(=O)NC1CCSc2ccc(F)cc12)O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1cccc(c1)C(C(=O)NC1CCSc2ccc(F)cc12)O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=C(NC1CCSc2ccc(F)cc21)C(O)c1ccccc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "90a620e5-1db6-4adf-8d6a-9e9d7a2d5996", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CN(C)S(=O)(=O)CCNC(=O)C1COc2ccccc2C1", "smiles_random": "O=S(=O)(N(C)C)CCNC(=O)C1Cc2ccccc2OC1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO=S(=O)(N(C)C)CCNC(=O)C1Cc2ccccc2OC1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CN(C)S(=O)(=O)CCNC(=O)C1COc2ccccc2C1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "c403a290-dde0-4003-a7c3-1dee3d74e719", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(=O)Nc1cccc(NC(=O)NCCc2nc(C(C)C)no2)c1", "smiles_random": "n1c(C(C)C)nc(o1)CCNC(Nc1cc(NC(=O)C)ccc1)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1c(C(C)C)nc(o1)CCNC(Nc1cc(NC(=O)C)ccc1)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(=O)Nc1cccc(NC(=O)NCCc2nc(C(C)C)no2)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "642152eb-eb7e-4a5d-8067-8d4d4325cace", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(NCC(c1ccccc1)C(C)(C)CO)c1cc(F)ccc1F", "smiles_random": "c1ccccc1C(C(C)(CO)C)CNC(c1cc(F)ccc1F)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1ccccc1C(C(C)(CO)C)CNC(c1cc(F)ccc1F)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(NCC(c1ccccc1)C(C)(C)CO)c1cc(F)ccc1F", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "33864186-f851-4d9a-b2d6-59dd6276e894", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(CCc1ccccc1)NC(=O)C(=O)NCc1ccccc1Cl", "smiles_random": "c1(c(Cl)cccc1)CNC(C(=O)NC(CCc1ccccc1)C)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(c(Cl)cccc1)CNC(C(=O)NC(CCc1ccccc1)C)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(CCc1ccccc1)NC(=O)C(=O)NCc1ccccc1Cl", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "f579bc65-f7a6-4f0f-bd9b-09fab80aaedb", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "COCC(NC(=O)C=Cc1ccc(Br)s1)C(N)=O", "smiles_random": "O=C(NC(COC)C(N)=O)C=Cc1ccc(Br)s1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO=C(NC(COC)C(N)=O)C=Cc1ccc(Br)s1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "COCC(NC(=O)C=Cc1ccc(Br)s1)C(N)=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "c8834fd1-be35-412d-8711-3fde4e9d3936", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCC(=O)Oc1ccc2c(C)c(Cc3ccccc3)c(=O)oc2c1C", "smiles_random": "O=C(CC)Oc1ccc2c(c1C)oc(c(Cc1ccccc1)c2C)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO=C(CC)Oc1ccc2c(c1C)oc(c(Cc1ccccc1)c2C)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCC(=O)Oc1ccc2c(C)c(Cc3ccccc3)c(=O)oc2c1C", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "b7f7336b-8f50-4da6-8b31-a4ca78b89735", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1cc(C)n2nc(SCC(=O)c3ccc4[nH]c(=O)[nH]c4c3)nc2n1", "smiles_random": "c12nc(SCC(=O)c3cc4[nH]c([nH]c4cc3)=O)nn2c(cc(C)n1)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc12nc(SCC(=O)c3cc4[nH]c([nH]c4cc3)=O)nn2c(cc(C)n1)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1cc(C)n2nc(SCC(=O)c3ccc4[nH]c(=O)[nH]c4c3)nc2n1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "75f74b66-fcbd-4e16-b5f2-7c367983afd1", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=C(c1cc(Cl)c2ccccc2c1O)N1CCCCC1c1ncc[nH]1", "smiles_random": "C1CC(c2[nH]ccn2)N(C(c2cc(Cl)c3c(cccc3)c2O)=O)CC1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1CC(c2[nH]ccn2)N(C(c2cc(Cl)c3c(cccc3)c2O)=O)CC1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=C(c1cc(Cl)c2ccccc2c1O)N1CCCCC1c1ncc[nH]1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "8d7a56a2-5476-40c9-a9e5-b81d511e60dd", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1cccc(-n2c(C)nnc2SCc2nc(-c3cccs3)no2)c1", "smiles_random": "n1c(-c2cccs2)nc(CSc2n(c(C)nn2)-c2cccc(C)c2)o1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1c(-c2cccs2)nc(CSc2n(c(C)nn2)-c2cccc(C)c2)o1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1cccc(-n2c(C)nnc2SCc2nc(-c3cccs3)no2)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "55f0fcf5-aca5-4fb9-9630-5d0101643f0b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCC(C)C(C(=O)N(C)CC(=O)Nc1c(C)cccc1C)c1ccccc1", "smiles_random": "c1ccc(c(c1C)NC(CN(C(=O)C(c1ccccc1)C(C)CC)C)=O)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1ccc(c(c1C)NC(CN(C(=O)C(c1ccccc1)C(C)CC)C)=O)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCC(C)C(C(=O)N(C)CC(=O)Nc1c(C)cccc1C)c1ccccc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "a176c2fc-92dd-4331-9e27-3c20fec7ebc7", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "COc1ccc(C2=C(C=O)C(c3ccccc3)c3ccccc3O2)cc1OC", "smiles_random": "O1C(c2ccc(OC)c(c2)OC)=C(C=O)C(c2ccccc21)c1ccccc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO1C(c2ccc(OC)c(c2)OC)=C(C=O)C(c2ccccc21)c1ccccc1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "COc1ccc(C2=C(C=O)C(c3ccccc3)c3ccccc3O2)cc1OC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "a5a261a6-790e-4a46-98dd-45381da1a25b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCC1CN(C(=O)c2c(C)cc(=O)n(CC(=O)NC(C)C)c2C)CCO1", "smiles_random": "C1(CN(C(=O)c2c(C)n(CC(=O)NC(C)C)c(=O)cc2C)CCO1)CCC"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1(CN(C(=O)c2c(C)n(CC(=O)NC(C)C)c(=O)cc2C)CCO1)CCC\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCC1CN(C(=O)c2c(C)cc(=O)n(CC(=O)NC(C)C)c2C)CCO1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "a9a5e74a-94b1-4cc2-9635-3304d66d0496", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCc1cccc(C)c1NC(=O)C(C)S(=O)(=O)Cc1cccc(F)c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(F)cccc1CS(=O)(C(C)C(=O)Nc1c(cccc1C)CC)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(F)cccc1CS(=O)(C(C)C(=O)Nc1c(cccc1C)CC)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCc1cccc(C)c1NC(=O)C(C)S(=O)(=O)Cc1cccc(F)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "f03867a8-732e-41ce-947a-51a440e056c6", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "COc1ccccc1C(=O)N1CCCC(c2ncccc2S(C)(=O)=O)C1", "smiles_random": "C1CCN(C(=O)c2ccccc2OC)CC1c1ncccc1S(C)(=O)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1CCN(C(=O)c2ccccc2OC)CC1c1ncccc1S(C)(=O)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "COc1ccccc1C(=O)N1CCCC(c2ncccc2S(C)(=O)=O)C1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "a5e2bd08-e215-4055-b723-0b116fcadaae", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCC1CCCCN1C(=O)NC(c1ccc(OC)cc1)C1CCOCC1", "smiles_random": "c1(OC)ccc(C(C2CCOCC2)NC(N2C(CC)CCCC2)=O)cc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(OC)ccc(C(C2CCOCC2)NC(N2C(CC)CCCC2)=O)cc1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCC1CCCCN1C(=O)NC(c1ccc(OC)cc1)C1CCOCC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "6e88e7c1-343b-444d-802b-c402883ab394", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(c1ccc(NC(=O)N2CCN(Cc3ccccc3)CC2)cc1)N1CCOCC1", "smiles_random": "c1cc(ccc1C(N1CCOCC1)C)NC(N1CCN(Cc2ccccc2)CC1)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1cc(ccc1C(N1CCOCC1)C)NC(N1CCN(Cc2ccccc2)CC1)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(c1ccc(NC(=O)N2CCN(Cc3ccccc3)CC2)cc1)N1CCOCC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "00eff658-a1cc-45f5-be93-f84a16febd0c", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=C(NCC(c1cccnc1)N1CCc2ccccc2C1)C(=O)Nc1ccccc1", "smiles_random": "c1cc(NC(=O)C(NCC(c2cccnc2)N2Cc3c(cccc3)CC2)=O)ccc1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1cc(NC(=O)C(NCC(c2cccnc2)N2Cc3c(cccc3)CC2)=O)ccc1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=C(NCC(c1cccnc1)N1CCc2ccccc2C1)C(=O)Nc1ccccc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "5b763756-ca6b-4780-b23e-9a94439440cd", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "COc1ccccc1-c1nnc(SCC(=O)Nc2ccc3c(c2)OCCO3)o1", "smiles_random": "c1(OC)ccccc1-c1oc(nn1)SCC(=O)Nc1cc2c(cc1)OCCO2"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(OC)ccccc1-c1oc(nn1)SCC(=O)Nc1cc2c(cc1)OCCO2\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "COc1ccccc1-c1nnc(SCC(=O)Nc2ccc3c(c2)OCCO3)o1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "79a5e8f1-c66c-4067-b1a4-e07573af492b", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1ccc(-c2nc(C)c(C(=O)NC(c3ccc(F)cc3)C3CCCO3)s2)o1", "smiles_random": "C1(CCCO1)C(c1ccc(cc1)F)NC(c1sc(-c2ccc(C)o2)nc1C)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1(CCCO1)C(c1ccc(cc1)F)NC(c1sc(-c2ccc(C)o2)nc1C)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1ccc(-c2nc(C)c(C(=O)NC(c3ccc(F)cc3)C3CCCO3)s2)o1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "f9f19cbe-df24-4904-b653-a44d274bf475", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCCC(=O)N1CCCCC1c1nc2c(c(=O)[nH]1)CN(C(=O)C1CCCC1)CC2", "smiles_random": "c12c(c([nH]c(C3CCCCN3C(=O)CCC)n1)=O)CN(CC2)C(C1CCCC1)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc12c(c([nH]c(C3CCCCN3C(=O)CCC)n1)=O)CN(CC2)C(C1CCCC1)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCCC(=O)N1CCCCC1c1nc2c(c(=O)[nH]1)CN(C(=O)C1CCCC1)CC2", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "3964d2d4-3de8-46ee-92c2-c4673de00fcd", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCn1c(SCC(=O)NC(=O)NCc2ccccc2)nnc1-c1ccc(Cl)cc1", "smiles_random": "c1(ccc(cc1)Cl)-c1n(CC)c(nn1)SCC(NC(NCc1ccccc1)=O)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(ccc(cc1)Cl)-c1n(CC)c(nn1)SCC(NC(NCc1ccccc1)=O)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCn1c(SCC(=O)NC(=O)NCc2ccccc2)nnc1-c1ccc(Cl)cc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "881379b7-3317-4f7b-a235-1c2a98be30bf", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CC(C)Oc1cc2ccccc2cc1C(=O)N1CCn2c(nnc2-c2cccs2)C1", "smiles_random": "CC(C)Oc1cc2ccccc2cc1C(N1Cc2nnc(n2CC1)-c1sccc1)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCC(C)Oc1cc2ccccc2cc1C(N1Cc2nnc(n2CC1)-c1sccc1)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CC(C)Oc1cc2ccccc2cc1C(=O)N1CCn2c(nnc2-c2cccs2)C1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "edd306f6-708a-4619-886e-10597fb4c742", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCC(Oc1ccccc1F)C(=O)N(Cc1cccc(Cl)c1)C1CCS(=O)(=O)C1", "smiles_random": "C1C(N(Cc2cc(ccc2)Cl)C(C(CC)Oc2ccccc2F)=O)CS(C1)(=O)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1C(N(Cc2cc(ccc2)Cl)C(C(CC)Oc2ccccc2F)=O)CS(C1)(=O)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCC(Oc1ccccc1F)C(=O)N(Cc1cccc(Cl)c1)C1CCS(=O)(=O)C1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "9be80276-c5ca-4889-8914-42e03f1e4ce8", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1nnsc1C(=O)N1CCC(CNC(=O)C(C)(C)Oc2ccc(Cl)cc2)CC1", "smiles_random": "c1(Cl)ccc(cc1)OC(C)(C)C(=O)NCC1CCN(C(c2c(nns2)C)=O)CC1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(Cl)ccc(cc1)OC(C)(C)C(=O)NCC1CCN(C(c2c(nns2)C)=O)CC1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1nnsc1C(=O)N1CCC(CNC(=O)C(C)(C)Oc2ccc(Cl)cc2)CC1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "b29d086a-3683-455d-87a5-7fb2c22c9a66", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=C(COc1ccc(Br)cc1)Nc1ccc2c(c1)C(=O)N(CC1CCCO1)C2=O", "smiles_random": "C1(OCCC1)CN1C(c2ccc(cc2C1=O)NC(COc1ccc(cc1)Br)=O)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1(OCCC1)CN1C(c2ccc(cc2C1=O)NC(COc1ccc(cc1)Br)=O)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=C(COc1ccc(Br)cc1)Nc1ccc2c(c1)C(=O)N(CC1CCCO1)C2=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "da8295f8-512c-40c7-a633-f5fb93e37b06", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "COc1cc(C=NNC(=O)c2cc(C)n[nH]2)ccc1OC(=O)c1cccc(Br)c1", "smiles_random": "C(c1cc(ccc1)Br)(Oc1ccc(C=NNC(c2[nH]nc(c2)C)=O)cc1OC)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC(c1cc(ccc1)Br)(Oc1ccc(C=NNC(c2[nH]nc(c2)C)=O)cc1OC)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "COc1cc(C=NNC(=O)c2cc(C)n[nH]2)ccc1OC(=O)c1cccc(Br)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "1b941d07-0ffd-4da9-93c0-138a9648aa61", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=S(=O)(c1ccc(Cl)cc1)n1nc(-c2cccnc2)nc1NCc1ccc(F)cc1", "smiles_random": "c1(ccc(CNc2n(nc(n2)-c2cnccc2)S(=O)(c2ccc(Cl)cc2)=O)cc1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(ccc(CNc2n(nc(n2)-c2cnccc2)S(=O)(c2ccc(Cl)cc2)=O)cc1)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=S(=O)(c1ccc(Cl)cc1)n1nc(-c2cccnc2)nc1NCc1ccc(F)cc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "0d5481aa-9fff-442c-88ce-135352d03280", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "NS(=O)(=O)c1ccc(Br)c(C(=O)Nc2cccc(NC(=O)c3ccco3)c2)c1", "smiles_random": "O=C(c1cc(ccc1Br)S(=O)(=O)N)Nc1cccc(c1)NC(c1occc1)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nO=C(c1cc(ccc1Br)S(=O)(=O)N)Nc1cccc(c1)NC(c1occc1)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "NS(=O)(=O)c1ccc(Br)c(C(=O)Nc2cccc(NC(=O)c3ccco3)c2)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "d06498e9-c6fe-4b8d-8fe8-bfda001790f3", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1noc2nc(C3CC3)cc(C(=O)N3CCN(S(=O)(=O)c4cccs4)CC3)c12", "smiles_random": "c12c(cc(nc1onc2C)C1CC1)C(N1CCN(S(=O)(=O)c2sccc2)CC1)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc12c(cc(nc1onc2C)C1CC1)C(N1CCN(S(=O)(=O)c2sccc2)CC1)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1noc2nc(C3CC3)cc(C(=O)N3CCN(S(=O)(=O)c4cccs4)CC3)c12", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "d7ab036b-ef19-4ab3-8afd-4e23f6e6b0e5", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "CCOc1cc(C=Nc2c(C)n(C)n(-c3ccccc3)c2=O)cc(I)c1OC", "smiles_random": "c1cccc(c1)-n1c(c(c(n1C)C)N=Cc1cc(OCC)c(OC)c(c1)I)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1cccc(c1)-n1c(c(c(n1C)C)N=Cc1cc(OCC)c(OC)c(c1)I)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "CCOc1cc(C=Nc2c(C)n(C)n(-c3ccccc3)c2=O)cc(I)c1OC", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "a8142455-f0d4-492e-8c1b-f624dc650ff0", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1ccc(C(=O)CSc2nnc3c(=O)n(-c4ccc(Br)cc4)ccn23)c(C)c1", "smiles_random": "c1c(ccc(Br)c1)-n1c(c2n(cc1)c(SCC(=O)c1ccc(cc1C)C)nn2)=O"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1c(ccc(Br)c1)-n1c(c2n(cc1)c(SCC(=O)c1ccc(cc1C)C)nn2)=O\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1ccc(C(=O)CSc2nnc3c(=O)n(-c4ccc(Br)cc4)ccn23)c(C)c1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "8ad6858b-1011-42ab-89a9-010f32670fde", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "COC(=O)c1ccc(N=C2SC(CC(=O)Nc3ccc(Br)cc3)C(=O)N2C)cc1", "smiles_random": "C1(=Nc2ccc(cc2)C(OC)=O)N(C(C(CC(=O)Nc2ccc(Br)cc2)S1)=O)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nC1(=Nc2ccc(cc2)C(OC)=O)N(C(C(CC(=O)Nc2ccc(Br)cc2)S1)=O)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "COC(=O)c1ccc(N=C2SC(CC(=O)Nc3ccc(Br)cc3)C(=O)N2C)cc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "9840f579-8f80-4f2b-aec8-d281f720c7f1", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1ccc(S(=O)(=O)N(CC(=O)N2CCN(C)CC2)c2ccc(Br)cc2)cc1", "smiles_random": "CN1CCN(C(=O)CN(c2ccc(cc2)Br)S(=O)(=O)c2ccc(cc2)C)CC1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nCN1CCN(C(=O)CN(c2ccc(cc2)Br)S(=O)(=O)c2ccc(cc2)C)CC1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1ccc(S(=O)(=O)N(CC(=O)N2CCN(C)CC2)c2ccc(Br)cc2)cc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "3df3eb16-66ee-4cfe-b87e-8913832d6f07", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cc1cc(C)n(CC(=O)Nc2ccc(F)cc2)c(=O)c1S(=O)(=O)c1ccc(Br)cc1", "smiles_random": "c1(NC(Cn2c(cc(c(c2=O)S(=O)(=O)c2ccc(Br)cc2)C)C)=O)ccc(cc1)F"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(NC(Cn2c(cc(c(c2=O)S(=O)(=O)c2ccc(Br)cc2)C)C)=O)ccc(cc1)F\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cc1cc(C)n(CC(=O)Nc2ccc(F)cc2)c(=O)c1S(=O)(=O)c1ccc(Br)cc1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "f3359621-ab7e-473b-9db4-5a3c1ec8abfa", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "O=C1Nc2c(Cl)cc(Cl)cc2C1(O)c1sc(N2CCCCC2)nc1-c1cccs1", "smiles_random": "c1(C2(c3c(c(Cl)cc(c3)Cl)NC2=O)O)sc(nc1-c1cccs1)N1CCCCC1"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nc1(C2(c3c(c(Cl)cc(c3)Cl)NC2=O)O)sc(nc1-c1cccs1)N1CCCCC1\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "O=C1Nc2c(Cl)cc(Cl)cc2C1(O)c1sc(N2CCCCC2)nc1-c1cccs1", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
{"uuid": "cb2c25e9-7fcf-4899-a692-1abc7ff6725d", "question_category": "smiles_to_iupac", "sub_category": "zinc_random", "meta_data": {"smiles": "Cn1c(=O)c2c(nc(Br)n2CC(O)COc2ccc(Cl)cc2Cl)n(C)c1=O", "smiles_random": "n1(c(=O)n(c(c2n(c(nc12)Br)CC(O)COc1ccc(cc1Cl)Cl)=O)C)C"}, "prompt": "Write the IUPAC name of this molecule:\n\nn1(c(=O)n(c(c2n(c(nc12)Br)CC(O)COc1ccc(cc1Cl)Cl)=O)C)C\n\nWrite the IUPAC name only. Do not write any comments.", "answer": "Cn1c(=O)c2c(nc(Br)n2CC(O)COc2ccc(Cl)cc2Cl)n(C)c1=O", "answer_format": "string", "answer_range": null, "verification_method": "opsin", "ChemIQ": true}
